Guide to the Records of the Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Pt.2, Series A on Microfilm, 1918-1965
Records of the Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Pt.2, Series A on Microfilm.
- Series Survey Schedules
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 81., 1943; 120 (Reel 3)
    December 11, 1943. 9 frames.
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 156., 1943; 121 (Reel 3)
    December 9, 1943. 8 frames.
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 814., 1943; 122 (Reel 3)
    December 14, 1943. 12 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 814., 1943; 123 (Reel 3)
    December 10, 1943. 9 frames.
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 814., 1943; 124 (Reel 3)
    December 14, 1943. 9 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 806., 1943; 125 (Reel 3)
    December 13, 1943. 10 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 992., 1943; 126 (Reel 3)
    December 21, 1943. 15 frames.
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 154., 1944; 127 (Reel 3)
    January 7, 1944. 11 frames.
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 128., 1944; 128 (Reel 3)
    January 4, 1944. 14 frames.
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 140., 1944; 129 (Reel 3)
    January 5, 1944. 9 frames.
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 105., 1944; 130 (Reel 3)
    January 4, 1944. 13 frames.
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 144., 1944; 131 (Reel 3)
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 278., 1943; 132 (Reel 3)
    December 30, 1943. 11 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 834., 1943; 133 (Reel 3)
    December 27, 1943. 8 frames.
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 139., 1944; 134 (Reel 3)
    January 27, 1944. 23 frames.
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 125., 1944; 135 (Reel 3)
    February 3, 1944. 17 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 5., 1944; 136 (Reel 3)
    February 8, 1944. 19 frames.
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 917., 1944; 137 (Reel 3)
    February 12, 1944. 22 frames.
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 112., 1944; 138 (Reel 3)
    February 14, 1944. 12 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 590., 1944; 139 (Reel 3)
    February 17, 1944. 17 frames.
  - Employees' Information and General Factory Rules. Bantam Bearings Corporation of South Bend, IN., 1942; 140 (Reel 3)
    October 1942. 23 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 9., 1944; 141 (Reel 3)
    February 10, 1944. 39 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 764., 1944; 142 (Reel 3)
    March 11, 1944. 10 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 534., 1944; 143 (Reel 3)
    March 11, 1944. 21 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 941., 1944; 144 (Reel 3)
    March 7, 1944. 18 frames.
  - United Rubber Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 65., 1944; 145 (Reel 3)
    March 18, 1944. 20 frames.
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 927., 1944; 146 (Reel 3)
    March 18, 1944. 16 frames.
- Unpublished study-Women in Unions in a Midwest War Industry Area, 1943-1945 (continued) (Reel 4)
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 226 (American Leather Products Corporation)., 1 (Reel 4)
    n.d. 10 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 226 (Marmon-Herrington, Inc.), 2 (Reel 4)
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 226 (Foundry Unit, Indianapolis Works, International Harvester Company)., 3 (Reel 4)
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 226 (McQuay-Norris Manufacturing Company, Indianapolis Division)., 4 (Reel 4)
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 226 (Prest-O-Lite Battery Company)., 5 (Reel 4)
    n.d. 13 frames.
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 1001., 1944; 6 (Reel 4)
    April 1944. 13 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 97., 1944; 7 (Reel 4)
    April 6, 1944. 15 frames.
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 904., 1944; 8 (Reel 4)
    April 6, 1944. 12 frames.
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 813., 1944; 9 (Reel 4)
    November 14, 1944. 12 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 265., 1944; 10 (Reel 4)
    April 17, 1944. 12 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 492., 1944; 11 (Reel 4)
    April 19, 1944. 14 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 705., 1944; 12 (Reel 4)
    April 20, 1944. 13 frames.
  - United Rubber Workers of America, Local No. 110., 1944; 13 (Reel 4)
    May 5, 1944. 12 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 940., 1944; 14 (Reel 4)
    May 17, 1944. 14 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 662., 1944; 15 (Reel 4)
    May 20, 1944. 33 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 663., 1944; 16 (Reel 4)
    May 27, 1944. 20 frames.
  - United Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 107., 1944; 17 (Reel 4)
    June 3, 1944. 14 frames.
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 548., 1943; 18 (Reel 4)
    December 8, 1943. 17 frames.
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 1114., 1943; 19 (Reel 4)
    December 22, 1943. 11 frames.
  - Lake County Metal Trades Council of Waukegan, Illinois, AF of L., 1943; 20 (Reel 4)
    November 29, 1943. 13 frames.
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 377., 1943; 21 (Reel 4)
    December 29, 1943. 13 frames.
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 1118., 1944; 22 (Reel 4)
    March 11, 1944. 12 frames.
  - Evansville, Indiana Metal Trades Council, AF of L., 1944; 23 (Reel 4)
    April 21, 1944. 13 frames.
  - Constitution of the Evansville, Indiana Metal Trades Council., 1942; 24 (Reel 4)
    11 frames.
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 1231., 1944; 25 (Reel 4)
    April 1944. 12 frames.
  - International Automobile Workers of America, AF of L. Local No. 650., 1944; 26 (Reel 4)
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 969., 1944; 27 (Reel 4)
    May 1944. 14 frames.
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 1449., 1944; 28 (Reel 4)
    May 1944. 19 frames.
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AF of L, Local No. B-1048., 1944; 29 (Reel 4)
    May 13, 1944. 14 frames.
  - Federal Labor Union, AF of L, Local No. 18704., 1944; 30 (Reel 4)
    May 27, 1944. 14 frames.
  - International Union, United Automobile Workers of America, AF of L, Local No. 783., 1944; 31 (Reel 4)
    June 7, 1944. 12 frames.
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 1061., 1944; 32 (Reel 4)
    June 17, 1944. 34 frames.
  - By-Laws of the Cream City Lodge No. 1061, International Association of Machinists, AF of L., 33 (Reel 4)
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 66 (two copies)., 1944; 34 (Reel 4)
    June 28, 1944. 29 frames.
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AF of L, Local No. B-1169., 1944; 35 (Reel 4)
    July 1, 1944. 16 frames.
  - Constitution of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AF of L., 36 (Reel 4)
    n.d. 29 frames.
  - Constitution of Local Union B-1169 of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AF of L., 37 (Reel 4)
  - Booklet Entitled "The Controller" by the Square D Company of Milwaukee, WI., 1944; 38 (Reel 4)
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 66., 1944; 39 (Reel 4)
  - United Automobile Workers of America, AF of L, Local No. 736., 1944; 40 (Reel 4)
    July 6, 1944. 13 frames.
  - United Automobile Workers of America, AF of L, Local No. 322., 1944; 41 (Reel 4)
    July 22, 1944. 14 frames.
  - International Union, United Automobile Workers of America, AF of L, Local No. 209., 1944; 42 (Reel 4)
    July 22, 1944. 17 frames.
  - United Automobile Workers of America, AF of L, Local No. 232., 1944; 43 (Reel 4)
    July 29, 1944. 12 frames.
  - Smith Steel Workers Union, AF of L. Local No. 19806., 1944; 44 (Reel 4)
    August 5, 1944. 17 frames.
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 1628., 1944; 45 (Reel 4)
    August 28, 1944. 15 frames.
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 1696., 1944; 46 (Reel 4)
    August 29, 1944. 15 frames.
  - International Ladies Handbag, Luggage, and Novelty Workers Union, AF of L, Local No. 44., 1944; 47 (Reel 4)
    August 27, 1944. 13 frames.
  - International Moulders and Foundry Workers Union, AF of L, Local No. 233., 1944; 48 (Reel 4)
    August 30, 1944. 20 frames.
  - International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Local No. 1796., 1944; 49 (Reel 4)
    September 8, 1944. 20fs.
  - United Automobile Workers of America, AF of L, Local No. 477., 1944; 50 (Reel 4)
    September 25, 1944. 14 frames.
  - Federal Labor Union, AF of L, Local No. 22636., 1944; 51 (Reel 4)
    September 29, 1944. 15 frames.
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AF of L, Local No. 713., 1944; 52 (Reel 4)
    September 15, 1944. 15 frames.
  - By-Laws and Working Rules of Local Union No. B-713, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AF of L., 1943; 53 (Reel 4)
    February 16, 1943. 11 frames.
- Unpublished study-Women in Unions in a Midwest War Industry Area, 1943-1945 (continued); War Industry Communities Surveys (Reel 5)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AF of L, 1 (Reel 5)
    September 15, 1944. 12 frames.
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local No. 1111., 1944; 2 (Reel 5)
    July 1, 1944. 25 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 335., 1944; 3 (Reel 5)
    June 29, 1944. 12 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 248., 1944; 4 (Reel 5)
    June 16, 1944. 19 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 469., 1944; 5 (Reel 5)
    June 19, 1944. 13 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 409., 6 (Reel 5)
    n.d. 11 frames.
  - UAW-CIO, Local No. 75., 1944; 7 (Reel 5)
    19 frames.
  - United Steelworkers of America, CIO, Local No. 1673., 1944; 8 (Reel 5)
    July 29, 1944. 16 frames.
  - United Steelworkers of America, CIO, Local No. 1258., 1944; 9 (Reel 5)
  - United Steelworkers of America, CIO, Local No. 65., 1944; 10 (Reel 5)
    October 6, 1944. 17 frames.
- Series War Industry Communities Survey - Subject Files
  - Absenteeism Listed by Community, 1943; 11 (Reel 5)
  - Accidents and Safety Measures Listed by Community, 1943; 12 (Reel 5)
  - Child Care Listed by Community, 1943; 13 (Reel 5)
    21 frames.
  - Community Services Listed by Community, 1943; 14 (Reel 5)
  - Economic Character of Areas Listed by Community, 1943; 15 (Reel 5)
    20 frames.
  - Employment of Negroes Listed by Community, 1943; 16 (Reel 5)
    6 frames.
  - Employment of Women Listed by Community, 1943; 17 (Reel 5)
    10 frames.
  - Farm Labor Listed by Community., 1943; 18 (Reel 5)
    September 1943. 2 frames.
  - Food Facilities Listed by Community, 1943; 19 (Reel 5)
  - Health and Medical Facilities Listed by Community, 1943; 20 (Reel 5)
  - Hours of Work Listed by Community, 1943; 21 (Reel 5)
  - Housing Listed by Community, 1943; 22 (Reel 5)
    27 frames.
  - Labor Organizations Listed by Community, 1943; 23 (Reel 5)
  - Labor Supply and Demand Listed by Community, 1943; 24 (Reel 5)
    28 frames.
  - Part Time Workers Listed by Community, 1943; 25 (Reel 5)
- Series Program for Community Surveys
  - Suggested Program for State of Community Study and Action Group on War and Postwar Problems of Women Workers., 26 (Reel 5)
  - Certain Suggested Community Activities Related to the Points Listed in the Reconversion Blueprint for Women., 27 (Reel 5)
  - The Economic Responsibilities of Employed Married Women., 1946; 28 (Reel 5)
    February 1946. 1 frame.
  - The Economic Responsibilities of Employed Widowed or Divorced Women., 1946; 29 (Reel 5)
    February 1946. 2 frames.
  - Women's Bureau Post War and Optimum Hour Study., 30 (Reel 5)
  - Comments from Interviews on Why Women Are Going to Continue to Work, Post-War Studies., 31 (Reel 5)
  - Data Sought in Various Questionnaires relating to Post-War Intentions of Women Workers., 32 (Reel 5)
  - The Economic Responsibilities of Women Workers as Shown by a Women's Bureau Study of Women War Workers and Their Postwar Employment Plans., 1946; 33 (Reel 5)
  - The Economic Responsibilities of Employed Single Women., 1946; 34 (Reel 5)
  - Prepared Remarks by Dorothy Bellanca, Vice President of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America at the New York Times Hall in a Panel Discussion on "The Economic Future of Women.", 35 (Reel 5)
  - Preliminary Summary, Highlights of the Post-War Study--Nine Areas., 1945; 36 (Reel 5)
    May 14, 1945. 32 frames.
  - Community Notes to Mrs. De Camp., 1943; 37 (Reel 5)
    44 frame.
  - Subjects Covered in Community Surveys Made by Women's Bureau Agents during World War II, 38 (Reel 5)
  - Summary of Selected Community Surveys Made by the Women's Bureau, US Department of Labor., 1943; 39 (Reel 5)
    November 29, 1943. 2 frames.
  - Child Care, 40 (Reel 5)
  - Housing, 41 (Reel 5)
  - Transportation, 42 (Reel 5)
    1 frame.
  - Recreation Facilities, 43 (Reel 5)
  - Article Entitled "Wartime Washington" by William H. Nicholas., 1943; 44 (Reel 5)
    September 1943. 15 frames.
  - Article Entitled "I Was a Worker" by Mary G. Currier., 1943; 45 (Reel 5)
    March 29, 1943. 5 frames.
  - Notes on Upgrading of War Plants, Navy and Ship Yards, 1943; 46 (Reel 5)
    9 frames.
  - Article Entitled "Accomodations for the Ladies" by Anne Grayson Williams., 47 (Reel 5)
  - List of Community Surveys by the Women's Bureau., 48 (Reel 5)
  - Women's Bureau Visits to Connecticut Communities--Recreational Facilities, 1942; 49 (Reel 5)
  - Recreational Facilities in Fort Worth, Texas@ Parsons, Kansas@ Memphis, Tennessee@ Savanna and Hoover, Illinois@ Akron, Ohio@ and Baltimore, Maryland, 1942; 50 (Reel 5)
  - Methods and Hiring and Training Women Employed by War Industries., 1942; 51 (Reel 5)
    July 1, 1942. 4 frames.
  - Recommendations Concerning Living Needs of Women Workers in Rural Community Plant Areas., 1942; 52 (Reel 5)
    May 22, 1942. 15 frames.
  - Proposed Plan for Cooperation between the Women's Bureau and the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America., 53 (Reel 5)
  - Care for Children of Employed Mothers in Defense Areas Visited by the Women's Bureau., 1942; 54 (Reel 5)
    January 29, 1942. 3 frames.
  - Program for National Public Housing Conference., 55 (Reel 5)
  - Recreational Facilities in Industrial War Areas as Reported by Women's Bureau Agents, 1943; 56 (Reel 5)
    17 frames.
  - Recreation Listed by Community, 1943; 57 (Reel 5)
    14 frames.
  - Schools and Educational Facilities Listed by Community., 1943; 58 (Reel 5)
    June 1943. 2 frames.
  - Training Program Listed by Community, 1943; 59 (Reel 5)
  - Transportation Listed by Community, 1943; 60 (Reel 5)
  - Turnover Listed by Community, 1943; 61 (Reel 5)
  - Types of Workers Listed by Community, 1943; 62 (Reel 5)
  - Wages Listed by Community, 1943; 63 (Reel 5)
  - Note Cards Filled Out by Women Workers Listing Their Current Job and Their Postwar Job Desires and Their Reason for Wanting That Job., 64 (Reel 5)
    n.d. 16 frames.
  - Note Cards Describing Discriminatory Practices against Women., 65 (Reel 5)
- Series Geographical Files
  - Connecticut, 1940-1944; 66 (Reel 5)
    Includes Estimated Impact of Demobilization; Evidences of 1944 Cutbacks in Connecticut; Women War Workers in Connecticut; Employment of Wage Earners; Industrial Readjustment of Women Workers; List of Industrial Plants and Plant Sites to Be Disposed of by the Defense Plant Corporation; Employees in Manufacturing in Connecticut; Connecticut State Labor Laws for Women; and the Employment Status of Women in Connecticut in 1940. 26 frames.
  - Massachusetts, 1944; 67 (Reel 5)
    Includes Child Care Problems; Worker's Comments; Listing of Women Reporting on Desire to Change Occupations; Estimated Impact of Demobilization; List of Industrial Plants and Plant Sites to Be Disposed of by the Defense Plant Corporation, and Massachusetts State Labor Laws for Women. 57 frames.
- War Industry Communities Survey (continued); Geographical Files (Reel 6)
  - New York, 1 (Reel 6)
    n.d. Includes General Comments of Workers; Child Care Problems; Reasons for Women Planning on Stopping Work after the War; Postwar Employment Expectations for Women Employed in Erie County, New York in 1944; and Note Cards Listing Plants Employing Women Workers in Buffalo, Lockport, Syracuse, and Rochester, New York. 59 frames.
  - Pennsylvania, 2 (Reel 6)
    n.d. Includes Industrial Readjustment of Women Workers in Pennsylvania; Estimated Impact of Demobilization, Women War Workers in Pennsylvania Employees in Manufacturing in Pennsylvania; Pennsylvania State Labor Laws for Women; and Note Cards Listing Plants Employing Women in Pennsylvania. 25 frames.
  - Alabama, 3 (Reel 6)
    n.d. Includes General Comments of Workers. 6 frames.
  - West Virginia, 4 (Reel 6)
    n.d. Includes Note Cards Listing Plants Employing Women in Huntington. 4 frames.
  - Maryland, 5 (Reel 6)
    n.d. Areas Include Elkton, Aberdeen, and Edgewood, Maryland; Ravenna, Ohio; Charlestown, Jeffersonville, Walkerton, Kingsbury, and Burns City, Indiana; Marion, Herrin, Crab Orchard Lake, Joliet, Wilmington, Elwood, Alton, Rock Island, and Moline, Illinois; Burlington, Iowa; St. Louis, Missouri; Milan, Jackson, Humbolt, and Nashville, TN; San Diego, CA; Little Rock, Jacksonville, and Texarkana, AR; Shreveport and Minden, LA; Jackson and Flora, MS; Huntsville, Talladega, Childersburg, and Sylacauga, AL; Macon, GA; and Dublin, Radford, and Pulaski, VA. Information Includes the Agencies Active in These Areas; the Date of the Women's Bureau Report on the Area; the Character of the Area; Data on the Labor Supply, Housing, Food Supply, Transportation and Recreation Facilities, and Sanitation; and General Welfare of the Workers in the Area. 25 frames.
  - Maryland, 6 (Reel 6)
    n.d. Includes General Comments by Workers; Financial COmments of Women Workers in Baltimore along with Facts regarding their marital status, age, and number of children; Postwar Employment Expectations of Women Employed in the Baltimore Area; and the Desire of Women War Workers in Baltimore Area for Postwar Jobs. 217 frames.
  - Program for the Southern War Labor Conference., 1943; 7 (Reel 6)
    January 16-17, 1943. 4 frames.
  - Newspaper Clippings regarding the Southern War Labor Conference., 1943; 8 (Reel 6)
    January 1943. 7 frames.
  - General Notes on Labor Organizations in Region VII., 9 (Reel 6)
  - Savannah, Georgia., 1943; 10 (Reel 6)
    May 12, 1943. Includes Sources of Information; List of Persons Interviewed; List of Plants Visited; Union Organization and Attitudes toward Women Workers; Transportation Facilities; Food Supplies; Health Facilities; Housing, Recreation and Child Care. 39 frames.
  - Brunswick, GA, 1943; 11 (Reel 6)
    February 1, 1943. Includes Working Hours Controversy. 4 frames.
  - Macon, Georgia Defense Area, 1942; 12 (Reel 6)
    April 1942. Includes Housing for Women; Eating Facilities; Health Care; Recreation; List of Persons Interviewed; Sanitary and Transportation Facilities; Child Care; Education Facilities; and the Bibb County Citizen's Defense Council. 18 frames.
  - Amoco Road Maps of Florida, NC, SC, and Georgia., 13 (Reel 6)
    n.d. 9 frames.
  - Map of Greater Macon Area, GA., 14 (Reel 6)
  - Consolidated Tours Map of Florida., 15 (Reel 6)
  - Consolidated Tours Map of the East Coast of the US., 16 (Reel 6)
  - Pamphlets Relating to Macon, GA., 17 (Reel 6)
  - A Summary of the Development of National Defense Units In and Near Macon, GA., 1942; 18 (Reel 6)
    January 19, 1942. 2 frames.
  - Macon, GA, 19 (Reel 6)
    n.d. Includes List of Persons Interviewed; Sanitary and Transportation Facilities; Housing; Eating Facilities; Child Care; Health and Education Facilities; and Recreation. 29 frames.
  - Mississippi, 20 (Reel 6)
    n.d. Includes General Notes on Employment of Women in Mississippi; Housing; Educational and Recreational Facilities; Summary Report on the Flora, Mississippi Defense Area; Population Increases; Agencies Coordinating Facilities Needed for the Influx of Women Workers; Transportation Facilities; Child Care; Health Facilities; Comments on the Office of Civilian Defense and YWCA in Jackson, MS; List of Persons Contacted; Newspaper Clippings; Statistical Information for Jackson, MS; List of Manufacturers Operating in Jackson, MS; and Jackson, MS Citizen's Defense Corps General Training Course. 129 frames.
  - Charleston, SC, 21 (Reel 6)
    n.d. Includes Union Attitudes regarding Labor Problems and Selective Service Problem; Job Training Facilities; Transportation, Health and Educational Facilities; Housing; Recreational Facilities; and Child Care. 34 frames.
  - Memphis, TN Area, 22 (Reel 6)
    n.d. Includes Industrial Pattern of Memphis; Housing; Transportation and Recreational Facilities; National Defense Training Programs; Maps of Tennessee and Surrounding Area; Annual Report of the Memphis Housing Authority; List of Chief War Production Plants in Memphis and Number of Women Employed by Them; and Labor Supply in Memphis. 57 frames.
- Geographical Files (continued) (Reel 7)
  - Milan, TN Defense Area, 1942; 1 (Reel 7)
    March 1942. Includes Industrial Pattern of the Area; Transportation Facilities; Housing; Child Care; Health Facilities; and Facilities for Education, Recreation, and Welfare. 49 frames.
  - Jackson, TN: Defense Council., 2 (Reel 7)
  - Industrial Survey of Humbolt, Gibson County, TN., 1940; 3 (Reel 7)
    Includes General Physical Prospective; Financial Situation; Accomodations; Services Available; Industrial Situation; and Living Conditions. 14 frames
  - Notes on Milan and Humbolt, TN., 4 (Reel 7)
  - List of Industries in Jackson, TN and Vicinity, 1942; 5 (Reel 7)
    February 1942. 1 frame.
  - General Information Manual for Employees. Proctor & Gamble Defense Corporation Defense Plant., 6 (Reel 7)
  - Information Booklet from the Jackson, TN Chamber of Commerce, 1940; 7 (Reel 7)
    7 frames
  - Nashville, TN, 8 (Reel 7)
    n.d. Includes Industrial Pattern of Nashville Area; Labor Supply; National Defense Training Program; Housing; Recreational and Transportation Facilities; Brief Outline of the Type of Training Offered in National Defense Courses; and Bulletin on the Selective Service and the Supply of Manpower. 12 frames.
  - Detroit, MI, 9 (Reel 7)
    n.d. Includes Postwar Comments by Workers with Facts on Their Marital Status, Age, Income, and Number of Children and the Postwar Needs and Expectations of Women for Employment in the Detroit-Willow Run Labor Market Area. 62 frames.
  - Ohio, 10 (Reel 7)
    n.d. Includes Industrial Readjustments of Women Workers in Ohio; Employment Figures for Women Working in Ohio War Plants; Estimated Impact of Demobilization of Ohio; Area Statements for Cleveland, Dayton, Youngstown, Akron, Toledo, Cincinnati, Columbus, and Canton by the War Manpower Commission Listing Major Industries, Employment Prospects, Jobs Immediately Available, and Major Firms; and Ohio State Labor Laws for Women. 25 frames.
  - Akron, OH, 11 (Reel 7)
    n.d. Includes Industrial Pattern for the Akron Area; Labor Supply; Housing; Transportation and Recreational Facilities; and National Defense Training Programs. 13 frames.
  - Cleveland, OH., 1942; 12 (Reel 7)
    March 1942. Includes National Defense Training Programs; Training of Women Inspectors; and Report on Women Workers in the Postwar Period by the War Manpower Commission. 24 frames.
  - Columbus, OH., 1942; 13 (Reel 7)
    March 1942. Includes Industrial Pattern of the Area; Labor Supply; National Defense Training Programs; Housing; Transportation and Recreational Facilities; and Child Care. 8 frames.
  - Ravenna, OH Defense Area, 1942; 14 (Reel 7)